<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<products><product><sku>505873497501</sku><name>Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers (Pair) Walnut</name><description>Key features:

    WhatHiFi 5-Star bookshelf speakers
    Exceptional value for money with advanced features for the price point
    Curved braced cabinets help to eliminate vibrations and dissipate standing waves
    Gold-plated bi-wire connection separates high and low frequencies for enhanced clarity
    Dual reflex ports enhance overall bass response and clarity

5-year warranty &amp; 30-day money-back guarantee included


            
Overview:
The Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers are clear and precise with unmatched sound reproduction at their level. They boast curved braced cabinets that not only allude to the premium aesthetic qualities of higher-priced speakers but also help to reduce unwanted cabinet vibrations and dissipate derogatory standing waves that can negatively affect your sound. The five-inch Kevlar mid/bass driver and one-inch textile tweeter work effortlessly together offering sparkling highs and full controlled lows revealing details in your favourite tracks that may have previously gone unheard. The gold-plated bi-wireable binding posts a trait usually only found at higher price ranges ensure complete versatility in your set-up and will benefit those who aim to achieve a precise and clean sound where high and low frequencies blend harmoniously without a fight for air space.</description><brand>Wharfedale</brand><category>Sound &amp; Vision|Home Audio &amp; HiFi Separates|Speakers &amp; Subwoofers</category><price>180.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUsAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>504048423208</sku><name>Cello C50WS4K 50" inch Smart WiFi WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV Freeview Play FRAMELESS</name><description>50″ Smart WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV with Freeview Play and Frameless Bezel

    50” 4K Ultra HD LED TV
    LG’s Smart operating system, WebOS Hub built-in
    Download apps through the web browser
    Freeview HD by Aerial &amp; also a Satellite tuner built-in with Freesat
    Bluetooth connectivity (easily add a Bluetooth soundbar)
    Freeview Play with 100 channels and 20,000 hours of free on-demand content
    3 x HDMI inputs for your external devices and consoles
    Can be wall mounted (200mm x 100mm bracket &amp; 4 pcs M5 X8 not included)


The built-in Smart platform, developed by LG, allows you to browse the web and download all your favourite entertainment apps, so you can stream directly to the TV. From Netflix, Prime Video and Disney Plus to YouTube and catch-up apps like BBC iPlayer and ITVx, a world of entertainment awaits.

With Freeview Play you can watch an impressive 60,000+ hours of TV and over 1,500 boxsets, across your favourite on-demand players. All for free.

With the built-in Bluetooth connectivity, you can add a Bluetooth soundbar to the TV. This means cinema sound can be enjoyed without the need for untidy cables. The built-in satellite tuner with Freesat provides access to over 170 channels with 100% channel coverage on a subscription-free basis. Plus, you’ll find your favourite on-demand players all in one place. You will just need to purchase and install your own satellite dish/cabling. The ultimate flat-screen TV with its super-slim bezel and lightweight design is ideal for wall mounting and easy maneuverability


Specification
Screen Size 	50″
Freeview Play 	Yes
DVD Player 	No
USB 	Yes – playback only
Contrast Ratio 	5000:1
Brightness 	250
Max Resolution 	3840 x 2160
Speakers 	2 x 8W
Smart 	Yes
Max Power 	120W
Energy Rating 	‘G – 71 watts on working and 0.5 watt standby power consumption
HDMI 	3
Inputs 	RF Antenna, HDMI X3, CVBS, USB x 2, RJ45
Outputs 	Digital Audio Out, Earphone Out
VESA 	200mm x 100mm
Dimension w/stand 	W 1110 x H 733 x D 268 mm
Dimensions w/o stand 	W 1110 x H 644 x D 34 mm
Weight 	9.1kg</description><brand>Cello</brand><category>Sound &amp; Vision|TVs</category><price>462.99</price><quantity>7</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DOkAAeSwt3BpwSw9/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>5058048349204</sku><name>Coffee Machine Espresso Machine Coffee Maker Cappuccino Milk Frother 20 Bar 1.8L</name><description>✅ 20Bar High-Pressure Extraction
Equipped with a professional high-pressure water pump, it delivers a stable 20Bar extraction pressure to instantly penetrate coffee grounds, fully releasing the aroma and oils of coffee beans. It easily  restoring the rich flavor of authentic espresso—every sip rivals the quality of specialty café drinks.
✅ 1.8L Large-Capacity Removable Water Tank
No need for frequent refills; a full tank can make multiple cups for the whole family, easily handling daily use and small gatherings. The semi-transparent design lets you check water levels at a glance, and the detachable structure, paired with a separate drip tray, makes refilling and cleaning a breeze—saving time and effort.
✅ Food-Grade Stainless Steel Manufacturing
The body and core contact parts are made of food-grade stainless steel, which is corrosion-resistant, high-temperature resistant, and durable. It eliminates residual odors, ensuring every cup of coffee is pure and safe, balancing premium texture with practicality.
🛠️ All-Inclusive Accessories · Unlock Diverse Coffee Experiences
The machine comes with a complete set of professional accessories, so you can start your home barista journey right out of the box. It balances professionalism and convenience to suit 
☕ Scenario Adaptation · Perfect for Your Daily Moments
🌅 Morning Wake-Up: One-tap espresso, paired with milk for an energizing latte to chase away drowsiness and kickstart a productive day.
☕ Afternoon Relaxation: Brew a cup of freshly ground coffee with dessert, enjoying a moment of peaceful solitude and elevating your at-home ritual.
🥂 Friend Gatherings: Quick double-cup brewing and a variety of milk-based drinks let you host a cozy coffee party at home.
💼 Office Energy Boost: Fast capsule brewing eliminates waiting time, providing timely energy to enhance work efficiency.
📌 Product Specifications
Extraction Pressure: 20Bar high-pressure extraction
Water Tank Capacity: 1.8L large-capacity removable water tank</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home, Furniture &amp; DIY|Appliances|Coffee, Tea &amp; Espresso Makers|Espresso &amp; Cappuccino Machines</category><price>97.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/IJsAAeSwtj1pr-Co/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>4049023423478</sku><name>11.5" Portable DVD Player with 9.5" Large HD Swivel Screen High Volume Speaker</name><description>About this item
👨‍👩‍👧【Portable and Magical】-- Compact design makes it easy to carry out with you. Take it on your road trip and get double surprises both on and off the screen. portable DVD player can be easily swiveled as a tablet and mounted to the car headrest, brings tons of fun for your journey.
👨‍👩‍👧【5 Hrs Battery Life】-- Upgraded battery capacity to 2500mAh, you and your family can watch 1-2 movies without any worries. Our portable DVD player for car provide a certificated AC power adapter and car charger in the package, no more worries about the battery dying out when you are out.
👨‍👩‍👧【Protective and Gorgeous Screen】-- portable DVD player for kids adopts the HD Eye-protective Screen, and refuses the recycled screen, aiming at alleviating eye fatigue caused by the long use, more comfortable and protective screen for your kids’ eyes.
👨‍👩‍👧【All Regions &amp; Multi Formats】-- Supports CD,DVD,VCD,SVCD,CD±R/±RW,DVD±R/±RW from all region (Blu-ray and pirated discs are not supported); DVD player portable also support multi-media files via USB and SD Card (16-32GB), such as VOB, AVI, MPEG, MP3, WMA, JPEG.
👨‍👩‍👧【Dual Speakers &amp; Clear Sound】-- Portable dvd player with screen equipped with two high-power speakers, which makes the volume louder. There is a 3.5mm earphone jack on the right side of the portable dvd players so that you can get a concentrated and clearer sound for your private viewing.
👨‍👩‍👧【Easy Operation &amp; Seamless Viewing】-- DVD player has a simple operating system and a convenient remote control, making it an ideal companion for the kids and elderly. Never miss out on exciting plots, the Break-point memory function can ensure seamless connection of the plot.
👨‍👩‍👧【Premium Service &amp; Quick Response】-- We are committed to providing the best after-sales service to our customers. If you have any questions, concerns, or issues with the your device, we are here to help you 24 hours a day.

★Eye-protection LCD screen★: DVD player provide a 800*480 Swivel Screen with 270 degrees rotation and 180 degrees flip. The portable player can be swiveled as a tablet to attache to the car backseat to play.
★Super High Battery★: Upgrade battery capacity to 2 times as the original ones, ensures the 5 hours play time. Not enough? Free car charger provided in the package.
★Resume Play★: Support break-point memory function, make it possible to start from where you left at last time, no need to start again.
★Game Player★: This DVD player is more than a DVD player, we provide a free game controller in our package, kids also can use this to play 180 kinds of retro games, such as super Mario etc. Note: customer need do download game cd by yourself.
★Multi-Media★: Directly play in formats: CD, DVD, CD-R/RW, DVD-R/+R, DVD+RW/-RW, VCD, SVCD; USB and SD Card supported: MP3/WMA/WAV, JPEG, MPEG2/AVI, TXT.


The new version of portable DVD player.
3 years in portable DVD player make us understand your needs better and make prodcuts more better.

Your Home Cinema always with You:
Our Portable DVD Player has a built-in USB port that allows you to enjoy your favorite movies while travelling, camping, sightseeing,you can also copy your CD files to USB or SD card.
Improved battery:
Improved 2000mAh Lithium battery extend the play time to 5 hours,even the adapter was left at home,do not need to worry about losing battery power whilst watching a movie.

Break Point memory:
Break Point memory function make it possible to start from where you end at last time.
Sync to your TV Screen:
With the included AV cable, it's available to transmit the screen from DVD player to your TV to enjoy a bigger and clearer screen.
Fantastic Swivel Screen: portable DVD player with 9.5 inch 270° rotation and 180° flip screen make it possible to attach to the car headrest and make you enjoy your time when you are on boring road trip.

Package Including:
1x Portable DVD player
1x AV cable
1x Remote controller
1x Power adapter
1x Car charger
1x User manual</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sound &amp; Vision|DVD, Blu-ray &amp; Home Cinema|DVD &amp; Blu-ray Players</category><price>65.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PnMAAeSw5yJpzi5u/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>9501234567891</sku><name>2 Packs 6AH For Makita 18V Battery Li-Ion BL1830 BL1850 BL1840 BL1860B LXT400</name><description>Product Description


Features:

1. New and in a good condition.
2. Made of durable and reliable material, harmless to your health.
3. It is easy to use, convenient to carry with.
4. The best replacement for the old or damaged one.
5. A great assistant for electric tools.
6. Provide convenience to charge your electric tool anytime and anywhere.
7. It is suitable for Makita BL1815, BL1830, BL1835, LXT400, 194204-5, 194205-3, 194309-1.

Specifications:
Chemistry: Li-ion
Brand: For Makita
Model No.: BL1830
Condition: Brand new
Sub-Type: Replacement Battery
Voltage (V): 18V
Capacity: 6000mAh
Color: Black

 

Replace Original Makita Battery Code:

for MAKITA

194205-3, 194309-1, BL1815, BL1830, BL1840, LXT400

 

Fit Original Makita Model:

for MAKITA

for Makita BDF453SHE, for Makita BDF454Z, for Makita BHP452

for Makita BML184, for Makita BML185,

for Makita BST221Z, for Makita BTDW251Z, for Makita ML185, for Makita TD140D, for Makita TW251D

for Makita BCS550 Series:BCS550, BCS550Z,

for Makita BDA350 Series:BDA350, BDA350Z,

for Makita BDF451 Series:BDF451, BDF451Z,

for Makita BFR550 Series:BFR550L, BFR550Z,

for Makita BFR750 Series:BFR750, BFR750L, BFR750Z,

for Makita BFS450 Series:BFS450, BFS450RFE, BFS450Z,

for Makita BGA452 Series:BGA452, BGA452Z,

for Makita BHP451 Series:BHP451, BHP451SFE, BHP451Z,

for Makita BHP453 Series:BHP453, BHP453SHE,

for Makita BHP454 Series:BHP454, BHP454Z,

for Makita BHR202 Series:BHR202, BHR202RFE, BHR202Z,

for Makita BHR240 Series:BHR240, BHR240Z,

for Makita BHR241 Series:BHR241, BHR241Z,

for Makita BJR181 Series:BJR181, BJR181X, BJR181X1,BJR181Z,

for Makita BJR182 Series:BJR182, BJR182X, BJR182Z,

for Makita BJS130 Series:BJS130, BJS130Z,

for Makita BJV180 Series:BJV180, BJV180Z,

for Makita BPB180 Series:BPB180, BPB180Z,

for Makita BSS501 Series:BSS501, BSS501Z,

for Makita BSS610 Series:BSS610, BSS610SFE, BSS610X2,BSS610Z,

for Makita BSS611 Series:BSS611X, BSS611Z,

for Makita BTD140 Series:BTD140, BTD140SFE, BTD140Z,

for Makita BTD141 SeriesBTD141, BTD141Z,

for Makita BTD144 Series:BTD144, BTD144RFE, BTD144Z,

for Makita BTL061 Series:BTL061, BTL061Z,

for Makita BTL063 Series:BTL063, BTL063Z,

for Makita BTP140 Series:BTP140, BTP140Z,

for Makita BTW251 Series:BTW251, BTW251Z,

for Makita BTW253 Series:BTW253, BTW253Z,

for Makita BTW450 Series:BTW450, BTW450Z,

for Makita BDA350 Series:BUB182, BUB182Z,

for Makita BVR350 Series:BVR350, BVR350Z,

for Makita BVR450 Series:BVR450, BVR450Z,

for Makita BVR850 Series:BVR850, BVR850Z,

for Makita DF454 Series:DF454D, DF454DRFX, DF454DZ,

for Makita HP454 Series:HP454D, HP454DRFX, HP454DZ,

for Makita HR202 Series:HR202D, HR202DRFX, HR202DZK,

for Makita JR120 Series:JR120D, JR120DRF, JR120DZK,

for Makita ML184 Series:ML184(FlashLight), ML184,

for Makita MR100 Series:MR100, MR100W,

for Makita PB108 Series:PB108D, PB108DRFX, PB108DZ,

for Makita TD144 Series:TD144DRFX, TD144DZ,

for Makita TD251 Series:TD251DRFX, TD251DZ


Package Includes:
2 x 6000mAh Batter</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home, Furniture &amp; DIY|DIY Tools &amp; Workshop Equipment|Power Tool &amp; Air Tool Accessories|Power Tool Batteries</category><price>31.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/u6MAAeSwuXxorCS3/s-l1600.jpg</image></product></products>