<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<products><product><sku>505873497501</sku><product_name>Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers (Pair) Walnut</product_name><description>Key features:

    WhatHiFi 5-Star bookshelf speakers
    Exceptional value for money with advanced features for the price point
    Curved braced cabinets help to eliminate vibrations and dissipate standing waves
    Gold-plated bi-wire connection separates high and low frequencies for enhanced clarity
    Dual reflex ports enhance overall bass response and clarity

5-year warranty &amp; 30-day money-back guarantee included


            
Overview:
The Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers are clear and precise with unmatched sound reproduction at their level. They boast curved braced cabinets that not only allude to the premium aesthetic qualities of higher-priced speakers but also help to reduce unwanted cabinet vibrations and dissipate derogatory standing waves that can negatively affect your sound. The five-inch Kevlar mid/bass driver and one-inch textile tweeter work effortlessly together offering sparkling highs and full controlled lows revealing details in your favourite tracks that may have previously gone unheard. The gold-plated bi-wireable binding posts a trait usually only found at higher price ranges ensure complete versatility in your set-up and will benefit those who aim to achieve a precise and clean sound where high and low frequencies blend harmoniously without a fight for air space.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUsAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/mGUAAeSwTFBp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zN4AAeSw61hp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUwAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y7wAAeSwajBp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vQ8AAeSwhIJp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Wharfedale</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>505873497501</ean><condition>New</condition><price>180.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>504048423208</sku><product_name>Cello C50WS4K 50" inch Smart WiFi WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV Freeview Play FRAMELESS</product_name><description>50вҖі Smart WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV with Freeview Play and Frameless Bezel

    50вҖқ 4K Ultra HD LED TV
    LGвҖҷs Smart operating system, WebOS Hub built-in
    Download apps through the web browser
    Freeview HD by Aerial &amp; also a Satellite tuner built-in with Freesat
    Bluetooth connectivity (easily add a Bluetooth soundbar)
    Freeview Play with 100 channels and 20,000 hours of free on-demand content
    3 x HDMI inputs for your external devices and consoles
    Can be wall mounted (200mm x 100mm bracket &amp; 4 pcs M5 X8 not included)


The built-in Smart platform, developed by LG, allows you to browse the web and download all your favourite entertainment apps, so you can stream directly to the TV. From Netflix, Prime Video and Disney Plus to YouTube and catch-up apps like BBC iPlayer and ITVx, a world of entertainment awaits.

With Freeview Play you can watch an impressive 60,000+ hours of TV and over 1,500 boxsets, across your favourite on-demand players. All for free.

With the built-in Bluetooth connectivity, you can add a Bluetooth soundbar to the TV. This means cinema sound can be enjoyed without the need for untidy cables. The built-in satellite tuner with Freesat provides access to over 170 channels with 100% channel coverage on a subscription-free basis. Plus, youвҖҷll find your favourite on-demand players all in one place. You will just need to purchase and install your own satellite dish/cabling. The ultimate flat-screen TV with its super-slim bezel and lightweight design is ideal for wall mounting and easy maneuverability


Specification
Screen Size         50вҖі
Freeview Play         Yes
DVD Player         No
USB         Yes вҖ“ playback only
Contrast Ratio         5000:1
Brightness         250
Max Resolution         3840 x 2160
Speakers         2 x 8W
Smart         Yes
Max Power         120W
Energy Rating         вҖҳG вҖ“ 71 watts on working and 0.5 watt standby power consumption
HDMI         3
Inputs         RF Antenna, HDMI X3, CVBS, USB x 2, RJ45
Outputs         Digital Audio Out, Earphone Out
VESA         200mm x 100mm
Dimension w/stand         W 1110 x H 733 x D 268 mm
Dimensions w/o stand         W 1110 x H 644 x D 34 mm
Weight         9.1kg</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DOkAAeSwt3BpwSw9/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qawAAeSwShFppWtV/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ztwAAOSwG3dm9EMH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EqAAAOSwNORlaIbE/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ISQAAOSwsINlaIbX/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/wfEAAOSw~FVlaIXe/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Cello</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>504048423208</ean><condition>New</condition><price>462.99</price><quantity>7</quantity></product><product><sku>5058048349204</sku><product_name>Coffee Machine Espresso Machine Coffee Maker Cappuccino Milk Frother 20 Bar 1.8L</product_name><description>вң… 20Bar High-Pressure Extraction
Equipped with a professional high-pressure water pump, it delivers a stable 20Bar extraction pressure to instantly penetrate coffee grounds, fully releasing the aroma and oils of coffee beans. It easily  restoring the rich flavor of authentic espressoвҖ”every sip rivals the quality of specialty cafГ© drinks.
вң… 1.8L Large-Capacity Removable Water Tank
No need for frequent refills; a full tank can make multiple cups for the whole family, easily handling daily use and small gatherings. The semi-transparent design lets you check water levels at a glance, and the detachable structure, paired with a separate drip tray, makes refilling and cleaning a breezeвҖ”saving time and effort.
вң… Food-Grade Stainless Steel Manufacturing
The body and core contact parts are made of food-grade stainless steel, which is corrosion-resistant, high-temperature resistant, and durable. It eliminates residual odors, ensuring every cup of coffee is pure and safe, balancing premium texture with practicality.
рҹӣ пёҸ All-Inclusive Accessories В· Unlock Diverse Coffee Experiences
The machine comes with a complete set of professional accessories, so you can start your home barista journey right out of the box. It balances professionalism and convenience to suit 
вҳ• Scenario Adaptation В· Perfect for Your Daily Moments
рҹҢ… Morning Wake-Up: One-tap espresso, paired with milk for an energizing latte to chase away drowsiness and kickstart a productive day.
вҳ• Afternoon Relaxation: Brew a cup of freshly ground coffee with dessert, enjoying a moment of peaceful solitude and elevating your at-home ritual.
рҹҘӮ Friend Gatherings: Quick double-cup brewing and a variety of milk-based drinks let you host a cozy coffee party at home.
рҹ’ј Office Energy Boost: Fast capsule brewing eliminates waiting time, providing timely energy to enhance work efficiency.
рҹ“Ң Product Specifications
Extraction Pressure: 20Bar high-pressure extraction
Water Tank Capacity: 1.8L large-capacity removable water tank</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/IJsAAeSwtj1pr-Co/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gDIAAeSwv5Npr-Cq/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/A7sAAeSwprxpr-Cr/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/E3sAAeSwfLxpr-Ct/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DMAAAeSwV8lpr-Cu/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FdYAAeSwC0Jpr-Cv/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>5058048349204</ean><condition>New</condition><price>97.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4049023423478</sku><product_name>11.5" Portable DVD Player with 9.5" Large HD Swivel Screen High Volume Speaker</product_name><description>About this item
рҹ‘ЁвҖҚрҹ‘©вҖҚрҹ‘§гҖҗPortable and MagicalгҖ‘-- Compact design makes it easy to carry out with you. Take it on your road trip and get double surprises both on and off the screen. portable DVD player can be easily swiveled as a tablet and mounted to the car headrest, brings tons of fun for your journey.
рҹ‘ЁвҖҚрҹ‘©вҖҚрҹ‘§гҖҗ5 Hrs Battery LifeгҖ‘-- Upgraded battery capacity to 2500mAh, you and your family can watch 1-2 movies without any worries. Our portable DVD player for car provide a certificated AC power adapter and car charger in the package, no more worries about the battery dying out when you are out.
рҹ‘ЁвҖҚрҹ‘©вҖҚрҹ‘§гҖҗProtective and Gorgeous ScreenгҖ‘-- portable DVD player for kids adopts the HD Eye-protective Screen, and refuses the recycled screen, aiming at alleviating eye fatigue caused by the long use, more comfortable and protective screen for your kidsвҖҷ eyes.
рҹ‘ЁвҖҚрҹ‘©вҖҚрҹ‘§гҖҗAll Regions &amp; Multi FormatsгҖ‘-- Supports CD,DVD,VCD,SVCD,CDВұR/ВұRW,DVDВұR/ВұRW from all region (Blu-ray and pirated discs are not supported); DVD player portable also support multi-media files via USB and SD Card (16-32GB), such as VOB, AVI, MPEG, MP3, WMA, JPEG.
рҹ‘ЁвҖҚрҹ‘©вҖҚрҹ‘§гҖҗDual Speakers &amp; Clear SoundгҖ‘-- Portable dvd player with screen equipped with two high-power speakers, which makes the volume louder. There is a 3.5mm earphone jack on the right side of the portable dvd players so that you can get a concentrated and clearer sound for your private viewing.
рҹ‘ЁвҖҚрҹ‘©вҖҚрҹ‘§гҖҗEasy Operation &amp; Seamless ViewingгҖ‘-- DVD player has a simple operating system and a convenient remote control, making it an ideal companion for the kids and elderly. Never miss out on exciting plots, the Break-point memory function can ensure seamless connection of the plot.
рҹ‘ЁвҖҚрҹ‘©вҖҚрҹ‘§гҖҗPremium Service &amp; Quick ResponseгҖ‘-- We are committed to providing the best after-sales service to our customers. If you have any questions, concerns, or issues with the your device, we are here to help you 24 hours a day.

вҳ…Eye-protection LCD screenвҳ…: DVD player provide a 800*480 Swivel Screen with 270 degrees rotation and 180 degrees flip. The portable player can be swiveled as a tablet to attache to the car backseat to play.
вҳ…Super High Batteryвҳ…: Upgrade battery capacity to 2 times as the original ones, ensures the 5 hours play time. Not enough? Free car charger provided in the package.
вҳ…Resume Playвҳ…: Support break-point memory function, make it possible to start from where you left at last time, no need to start again.
вҳ…Game Playerвҳ…: This DVD player is more than a DVD player, we provide a free game controller in our package, kids also can use this to play 180 kinds of retro games, such as super Mario etc. Note: customer need do download game cd by yourself.
вҳ…Multi-Mediaвҳ…: Directly play in formats: CD, DVD, CD-R/RW, DVD-R/+R, DVD+RW/-RW, VCD, SVCD; USB and SD Card supported: MP3/WMA/WAV, JPEG, MPEG2/AVI, TXT.


The new version of portable DVD player.
3 years in portable DVD player make us understand your needs better and make prodcuts more better.

Your Home Cinema always with You:
Our Portable DVD Player has a built-in USB port that allows you to enjoy your favorite movies while travelling, camping, sightseeing,you can also copy your CD files to USB or SD card.
Improved battery:
Improved 2000mAh Lithium battery extend the play time to 5 hours,even the adapter was left at home,do not need to worry about losing battery power whilst watching a movie.

Break Point memory:
Break Point memory function make it possible to start from where you end at last time.
Sync to your TV Screen:
With the included AV cable, it's available to transmit the screen from DVD player to your TV to enjoy a bigger and clearer screen.
Fantastic Swivel Screen: portable DVD player with 9.5 inch 270В° rotation and 180В° flip screen make it possible to attach to the car headrest and make you enjoy your time when you are on boring road trip.

Package Including:
1x Portable DVD player
1x AV cable
1x Remote controller
1x Power adapter
1x Car charger
1x User manual</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PnMAAeSw5yJpzi5u/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/~aoAAeSw2Rtpzi5w/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eDcAAeSwjStpzi5x/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AfoAAeSwXZ5pzi5z/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/hOUAAeSwdJ9pzi51/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JmMAAeSwz5hpzi53/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>DVD Players</category><ean>4049023423478</ean><condition>New</condition><price>65.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>9501234567891</sku><product_name>2 Packs 6AH For Makita 18V Battery Li-Ion BL1830 BL1850 BL1840 BL1860B LXT400</product_name><description>Product Description


Features:

1. New and in a good condition.
2. Made of durable and reliable material, harmless to your health.
3. It is easy to use, convenient to carry with.
4. The best replacement for the old or damaged one.
5. A great assistant for electric tools.
6. Provide convenience to charge your electric tool anytime and anywhere.
7. It is suitable for Makita BL1815, BL1830, BL1835, LXT400, 194204-5, 194205-3, 194309-1.

Specifications:
Chemistry: Li-ion
Brand: For Makita
Model No.: BL1830
Condition: Brand new
Sub-Type: Replacement Battery
Voltage (V): 18V
Capacity: 6000mAh
Color: Black

 

Replace Original Makita Battery Code:

for MAKITA

194205-3, 194309-1, BL1815, BL1830, BL1840, LXT400

 

Fit Original Makita Model:

for MAKITA

for Makita BDF453SHE, for Makita BDF454Z, for Makita BHP452

for Makita BML184, for Makita BML185,

for Makita BST221Z, for Makita BTDW251Z, for Makita ML185, for Makita TD140D, for Makita TW251D

for Makita BCS550 Series:BCS550, BCS550Z,

for Makita BDA350 Series:BDA350, BDA350Z,

for Makita BDF451 Series:BDF451, BDF451Z,

for Makita BFR550 Series:BFR550L, BFR550Z,

for Makita BFR750 Series:BFR750, BFR750L, BFR750Z,

for Makita BFS450 Series:BFS450, BFS450RFE, BFS450Z,

for Makita BGA452 Series:BGA452, BGA452Z,

for Makita BHP451 Series:BHP451, BHP451SFE, BHP451Z,

for Makita BHP453 Series:BHP453, BHP453SHE,

for Makita BHP454 Series:BHP454, BHP454Z,

for Makita BHR202 Series:BHR202, BHR202RFE, BHR202Z,

for Makita BHR240 Series:BHR240, BHR240Z,

for Makita BHR241 Series:BHR241, BHR241Z,

for Makita BJR181 Series:BJR181, BJR181X, BJR181X1,BJR181Z,

for Makita BJR182 Series:BJR182, BJR182X, BJR182Z,

for Makita BJS130 Series:BJS130, BJS130Z,

for Makita BJV180 Series:BJV180, BJV180Z,

for Makita BPB180 Series:BPB180, BPB180Z,

for Makita BSS501 Series:BSS501, BSS501Z,

for Makita BSS610 Series:BSS610, BSS610SFE, BSS610X2,BSS610Z,

for Makita BSS611 Series:BSS611X, BSS611Z,

for Makita BTD140 Series:BTD140, BTD140SFE, BTD140Z,

for Makita BTD141 SeriesBTD141, BTD141Z,

for Makita BTD144 Series:BTD144, BTD144RFE, BTD144Z,

for Makita BTL061 Series:BTL061, BTL061Z,

for Makita BTL063 Series:BTL063, BTL063Z,

for Makita BTP140 Series:BTP140, BTP140Z,

for Makita BTW251 Series:BTW251, BTW251Z,

for Makita BTW253 Series:BTW253, BTW253Z,

for Makita BTW450 Series:BTW450, BTW450Z,

for Makita BDA350 Series:BUB182, BUB182Z,

for Makita BVR350 Series:BVR350, BVR350Z,

for Makita BVR450 Series:BVR450, BVR450Z,

for Makita BVR850 Series:BVR850, BVR850Z,

for Makita DF454 Series:DF454D, DF454DRFX, DF454DZ,

for Makita HP454 Series:HP454D, HP454DRFX, HP454DZ,

for Makita HR202 Series:HR202D, HR202DRFX, HR202DZK,

for Makita JR120 Series:JR120D, JR120DRF, JR120DZK,

for Makita ML184 Series:ML184(FlashLight), ML184,

for Makita MR100 Series:MR100, MR100W,

for Makita PB108 Series:PB108D, PB108DRFX, PB108DZ,

for Makita TD144 Series:TD144DRFX, TD144DZ,

for Makita TD251 Series:TD251DRFX, TD251DZ


Package Includes:
2 x 6000mAh Batter</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/u6MAAeSwuXxorCS3/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/mSMAAeSwlBZorCS4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/L5AAAeSwJR5orCS5/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/40UAAeSw~YporCS7/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xAgAAeSwOV5orCS7/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/krIAAeSwHEtorCS-/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Power Tool Accessories</category><ean>9501234567891</ean><condition>New</condition><price>31.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092475</sku><product_name>Bluetooth FM Transmitter Car Kit MP3 Player USB Charger Handsfree Adapter UK</product_name><description>Upgrade your driving experience with this multifunctional Car Charger Bluetooth adapter. Combining hands-free calling, music streaming, and rapid charging, itвҖҷs the perfect companion for every journey. Designed with Fast Charger BT 5.0 technology, it delivers high-speed charging while keeping your devices connected safely.


вӯҗ Key Features
Bluetooth 5.0 Connectivity: Stable, fast pairing with smartphones for calls, music, and navigation audio.
FM Transmitter Function: Stream your favorite playlists directly to your car stereo via FM radio.
Dual USB Fast Charging Ports: Supports rapid charging for multiple devices simultaneously.
MP3 Player Support: Play music from USB drives or SD cards effortlessly.
Hands-Free Calling: Clear audio with built-in microphone ensures safe driving.
Compact &amp; Universal Design: Fits all standard car cigarette lighter sockets and works with most vehicles.

рҹ“Ҡ Technical Specs
Bluetooth Version: 5.0
Input: DC 12-24V
Output: 5V/2.4A per USB port
Frequency Range: 87.5вҖ“108MHz
Compatible Formats: MP3/WMA/WAV
LED Display: Shows FM frequency and device info

рҹ’Ў Benefits
Charge your phone and other devices quickly with Fast Charger BT 5.0 technology.
Enjoy seamless music streaming without tangled wires.
Stay safe with hands-free calling while driving.
Compact design keeps your dashboard neat and organized.

рҹҺҜ Ideal For
Daily commuters who need fast device charging and music on the go.
Road trips and long drives requiring hands-free calls and entertainment.
Anyone who wants to upgrade an older car stereo to Bluetooth functionality.
Drivers with multiple devices needing simultaneous fast charging.

рҹҢҗ Vast Applications
Cars, SUVs, trucks, and other vehicles with cigarette lighter sockets.
Listening to music or podcasts from smartphones, USB drives, or SD cards.
Hands-free calls during work commutes, rideshare driving, or family trips.
Charging smartphones, tablets, GPS devices, power banks, and other USB devices.
Enhancing older car stereos with FM broadcasting and Bluetooth connectivity.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2FkAAeSwnNZpbks~/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4QAAAeSwYPtpbktl/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/v18AAeSw40tpbkth/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1jgAAeSwTb5pbks9/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qZ0AAeSwLmtpbktK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Mx8AAeSwGJ5pbktO/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092475</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097401</sku><product_name>Mini Pocket Umbrella Folding Compact Rain Windproof Anti UV 5 Folding Travel UK</product_name><description>Stay protected in every season with this sleek and ultra-portable Mini Pocket Compact Fold Umbrella. Designed for modern lifestyles, it combines Rain Windproof durability with Anti UV protection, making it the perfect everyday travel essential.


вӯҗ Key Features
рҹҢ§ Rain Windproof Design вҖ“ Strong frame for reliable performance in wind &amp; rain
вҳҖпёҸ Anti UV Protection вҖ“ Helps block harmful sun rays on hot days
рҹ‘ң Ultra Compact &amp; Pocket Size вҖ“ Easy to carry anywhere, anytime
вҡЎ Quick Open &amp; Fold вҖ“ Simple, hassle-free operation
рҹҺ’ Travel Case Included вҖ“ Clean and convenient storage
рҹ’Ә Durable Build вҖ“ Premium materials for long-term use

рҹ“Ҹ Technical Specifications
Type: 5-Fold Compact Umbrella
Material: Waterproof Fabric + Reinforced Metal Frame
Function: Rainproof, Windproof, Anti UV
Folded Size: Approx. 15вҖ“18 cm
Open Diameter: Approx. 90вҖ“95 cm
Weight: Lightweight &amp; portable
Included: Protective Travel Case

рҹҢҚ Ideal For
рҹҢ§ Rainy Days вҖ“ Stay dry during sudden showers
вҳҖпёҸ Super Sunny Days вҖ“ Reliable shade with Anti UV protection
рҹҚӮ Autumn &amp; Winter вҖ“ Handles wet and windy conditions
рҹҢё Spring Showers вҖ“ Perfect for unpredictable weather
рҹҢһ Summer Heat вҖ“ Use as a portable sunshade
рҹҢҰ All-Season Use вҖ“ One umbrella for every condition

рҹ”„ Vast Application of Usage
Designed to make your life easier, this umbrella is perfect for:

рҹҡ¶ Daily Use вҖ“ Commuting, school runs, office travel
рҹӣҚ Shopping Trips вҖ“ Stay comfortable while out and about
вңҲпёҸ Travel &amp; Holidays вҖ“ Compact size fits easily in luggage
рҹҡ— On-the-Go Protection вҖ“ Keep in your car or bag for emergencies
рҹҺү Outdoor Events вҖ“ Festivals, sports days, gatherings
рҹҸ• Outdoor Activities вҖ“ Walking, hiking, camping
рҹ‘ЁвҖҚрҹ‘©вҖҚрҹ‘§ For Everyone вҖ“ Suitable for men, women, and kids
рҹ‘ү No confusion, no hassle вҖ” one simple solution for all your weather needs


рҹҺҜ Why Choose This Umbrella?
вң” Dual-purpose Rain Windproof &amp; Anti UV protection
вң” Compact, lightweight, and easy to carry
вң” Reliable in all weather conditions
вң” Practical design for everyday convenience

рҹҡҖ Benefits YouвҖҷll Love
Stay dry and protected anytime, anywhere
Enjoy peace of mind with all-in-one weather protection
Carry effortlessly without bulk
Dependable performance you can trust</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/U-oAAeSwf8Fp43cb/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XGwAAeSwv5dp43ca/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YaQAAeSw8Zdp43cb/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eIUAAeSwzmBp43ca/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/NRgAAeSwo41p43cZ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fYwAAeSwpHRp43ca/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834097401</ean><condition>New</condition><price>18.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097418</sku><product_name>Bike Seat Cover Soft Gel Saddle Bicycle Padded Cushioned Extra Comfort UK</product_name><description>Soft Gel Bike Seat Cover Padded Cushion Saddle вҖ“ Universal Fit for Maximum Comfort рҹҡҙ
Upgrade your cycling experience with this premium Soft Gel Bike Seat Cover, designed to deliver exceptional Padded Comfort on every ride. Whether commuting, exercising, or riding long distances, enjoy a smoother, pain-free journey.

вӯҗ Key Features
Soft Gel Padding вҖ“ Advanced cushioning absorbs shock and reduces pressure
Padded Comfort Design вҖ“ Extra-thick padding for long rides
Secure Anti-Slip Fit вҖ“ Non-slip base with adjustable drawstring
Breathable Design вҖ“ Airflow channel reduces heat and moisture
Water-Resistant вҖ“ Protects from sweat and light rain
Universal Fit вҖ“ Fits most standard bike saddles
рҹ’Һ Premium Quality &amp; Material
High-grade soft gel with high-density memory foam
Premium Lycra fabric вҖ“ breathable and stretchable
Reinforced stitching for durability
Anti-slip textured base for stability
Maintains shape after long-term use
рҹ“җ Technical Specifications
Material: Soft Gel + High-Density Foam + Lycra Fabric
Size: Approx. 27.5 x 17 cm
Weight: Lightweight &amp; portable
Compatibility: Fits most bike saddles
Installation: Easy slip-on with drawstring
рҹҺҜ Ideal For
Daily commuters and city cyclists
Long-distance and endurance riders
Indoor cycling and spin classes
Mountain and road biking
Beginners needing extra comfort
рҹҢҚ Vast Applications
Road bikes вҖ“ long-distance comfort
Mountain bikes вҖ“ shock absorption
City bikes вҖ“ daily commuting
Exercise bikes вҖ“ home workouts
Hybrid bikes вҖ“ mixed terrain
Leisure cycling вҖ“ casual rides
Travel &amp; touring вҖ“ portable comfort
вң… Benefits
Ride longer without discomfort
Reduces pressure on sensitive areas
Improves performance and endurance
Quick installation вҖ“ no tools needed</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/r~QAAeSwYytp4Och/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gOoAAeSweFVp4Och/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WMIAAeSwcSpp4Oci/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MF0AAeSw2rlp4Oci/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/M7MAAeSwDeVp4Och/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ob0AAeSwFbNp4Oci/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834097418</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097500</sku><product_name>Anti Mosquito Insect &amp; Bug Repellent Bracelet Bands Silicone Wristband 1- 20 PK</product_name><description>вӯҗ Key Features
Effective Mosquito Protection вҖ“ Helps repel mosquitoes and insects naturally
Safe &amp; DEET-Free вҖ“ Infused with natural plant-based essential oils
Adjustable &amp; Flexible Fit вҖ“ Comfortable silicone design for adults and children
Long-Lasting Use вҖ“ Provides extended protection for hours
Portable &amp; Easy вҖ“ Wear on wrist, ankle, or attach anywhere
Multiple Colors вҖ“ Fun and vibrant options
Value Packs вҖ“ Available in 1вҖ“20 PCS options
рҹ“Ҡ Technical Specifications
Material: High-quality silicone
Active Ingredients: Natural essential oils (citronella, eucalyptus, etc.)
Size: One-size-fits-most (adjustable)
Usage Time: Several hours per band (varies by environment)
Application: Wrist, ankle, bags, strollers
Pack Options: 1, 5, 10, 15, or 20 pieces
вң… Benefits
No sprays, no skin irritation, no mess
Family-friendly for kids and adults
Lightweight, waterproof, and travel-ready
Great alternative to traditional repellents
рҹҺҜ Ideal For
Camping, hiking, fishing, and outdoor adventures
Travel, holidays, and picnics
Gardening, BBQs, and sports activities
Everyday use at home or school
рҹҢҚ Vast Applications of Usage
Outdoor: camping, trekking, cycling, beach trips
Home &amp; garden: backyard, lawn work, evening relaxation
Kids: school, playgrounds, daycare
Travel: airports, hotels, tropical destinations
Work: fishing, farming, construction, warehouses
Pet walks: parks, trails, wooded areas
Daily use: shopping, commuting, casual outings
рҹҡҡ Free Shipping
Fast &amp; reliable delivery
Secure packaging for safe arrival
No extra charges</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jS0AAeSwJyRp2OwQ/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tpgAAeSw1rlp2OwQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/3rAAAeSwFh9p2OwR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AyQAAeSwe5tp2OwQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qOsAAeSwF7Vp2OwR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1ZcAAeSw2L9p2OwR/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834097500</ean><condition>New</condition><price>13.99</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097517</sku><product_name>Juicer Lemon Squeezer Citrus Juice Hand Held Stainless Steel Fruit Orange</product_name><description>Key Features
Perfect Squeeze Technology вҖ“ Extracts maximum juice with minimal effort
Durable Stainless Steel Build вҖ“ Rust-resistant and long-lasting
Ergonomic Handle Design вҖ“ Comfortable grip for easy squeezing
No Seeds, No Mess вҖ“ Built-in filter keeps juice smooth
Easy to Clean вҖ“ Dishwasher safe and quick rinse cleaning
Used for Variety of Fruits вҖ“ Ideal for lemons, limes, and small oranges
рҹ“җ Technical Specifications
Material: Premium Stainless Steel
Type: Handheld Manual Juicer
Color: Silver
Size: Compact &amp; portable
Weight: Lightweight yet durable
Cleaning: Dishwasher safe
рҹ’Ў Benefits
Saves time compared to manual squeezing
Extracts more juice with less waste
Keeps hands clean and irritation-free
Ideal for home, bars, and restaurants
Compact for easy storage and travel
рҹҺҜ What It Is Ideal For
Making fresh lemon and lime juice
Preparing cocktails and refreshing drinks
Adding flavor to salads, marinades, and dishes
Baking desserts and pastries
Daily kitchen and professional use
рҹҢҚ Vast Applications of Usage
Beverages вҖ“ lemon water, smoothies, iced tea
Cooking вҖ“ seafood, chicken, sauces, vegetables
Salads вҖ“ fresh citrus dressings
Baking вҖ“ cakes, tarts, desserts
Bar use вҖ“ cocktails like margaritas &amp; mojitos
Natural cleaning вҖ“ eco-friendly lemon solutions
DIY beauty вҖ“ skincare and hair remedies
Outdoor use вҖ“ picnics, camping, travel</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bLYAAeSweM9p34ep/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1dQAAeSwJk1p34eq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/hMsAAeSwtV5p34eq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/cB0AAeSweFVp34eq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/w4UAAeSw9G5p34eq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fAMAAeSwcE5p34eq/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834097517</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340975905</sku><product_name>EMERGENCY HAMMER CAR WINDOW BREAKER SEATBELT CUTTER BREAK GLASS ESCAPE SAFETY UK</product_name><description>EMERGENCY HAMMER Car Window Breaker &amp; Seatbelt Cutter вҖ“ Essential Vehicle Escape Safety Tool (UK Stock)

Be fully prepared for unexpected emergencies with this highвҖ‘quality EMERGENCY HAMMER featuring a WINDOW BREAKER &amp; SEATBELT CUTTER. Designed for rapid response, this compact yet durable tool can make a critical difference when seconds matter.


вӯҗ Key Features
вң” 2-in-1 Emergency Design вҖ“ Heavy-duty window breaker &amp; seatbelt cutter in one compact tool
вң” Hardened Steel Hammer Head вҖ“ Instantly shatters side windows in emergency situations
вң” Sharp Concealed Blade вҖ“ Quickly cuts jammed or locked seatbelts
вң” Non-Slip Anti-Skid Handle вҖ“ Firm grip for safe and controlled use
вң” High-Visibility Red Body вҖ“ Easy to locate in stressful situations
вң” Protective Mounting Bracket вҖ“ Secure and convenient storage within reach
вң” Compact &amp; Lightweight вҖ“ Fits glove box, door pocket, or centre console

рҹ”§ Technical Specifications
Material: High-carbon hardened steel hammer head
Handle: Durable ABS with anti-slip grip
Blade: Stainless steel concealed safety blade
Length: Approx. 17cm
Weight: Approx. 130вҖ“150g
Colour: Red
Condition: Brand New
Stock Location: UK

рҹҢҚ Vast Application of Usage
This EMERGENCY HAMMER is suitable for a wide range of vehicles and emergency situations:

рҹҡ— Private cars &amp; family vehicles
рҹҡ• Taxis, Uber &amp; ride-share vehicles
рҹҡҡ Vans, trucks &amp; delivery fleets
рҹҡҢ Buses &amp; minibuses
рҹҡҗ Motorhomes &amp; caravans
рҹҡ“ Emergency &amp; service vehicles
рҹҡӨ Boats &amp; marine vehicles
рҹҸў Workplace fleet vehicles
рҹҺ’ Travel safety kits &amp; roadside emergency kits
Perfect for emergencies involving:

Vehicle submersion in water
Electrical or central locking failure
Car fires
Severe collisions
Jammed doors after impact

рҹӣЎ Key Benefits
вң” Enables fast escape when doors cannot be opened
вң” Cuts seatbelts instantly to prevent entrapment
вң” Provides peace of mind for drivers and passengers
вң” A small investment for potentially life-saving protection

рҹ“Ұ Package Includes
1 Г— EMERGENCY HAMMER
1 Г— Mounting Bracket</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VkAAAeSw8Udp0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rFoAAeSwxGxp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rJwAAeSwJQ1p0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/CcEAAeSw7mhp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vb4AAeSwAVRp0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/T8EAAeSwQHtp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>4048340975905</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.99</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092451</sku><product_name>Women's Fishnet Thigh-High Stockings Tights Suspender Pantyhose Stocking Hosiery</product_name><description>рҹ”Ҙ PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Add elegance and style to your outfit with these womenвҖҷs lace garter stockings, designed with a sheer fishnet finish and decorative floral lace top. Made from a soft nylon and polyester blend, these stockings provide comfort, flexibility, and a fashionable look.

Perfect for pairing with dresses, skirts, costumes, or evening outfits, these thigh-high stockings add a stylish finishing touch to any wardrobe.

вӯҗ KEY FEATURES
вң… Soft Stretch Material вҖ“ Comfortable nylon and polyester blend
вң… Elegant Lace Top вҖ“ Stylish floral pattern design
вң… Sheer Fishnet Style вҖ“ Modern fashionable appearance
вң… One Size Fit вҖ“ Flexible stretch design fits most
вң… Lightweight &amp; Breathable вҖ“ Comfortable for extended wear
вң… Over Knee Length вҖ“ Classic thigh high styling
вң… Multiple Styles Available вҖ“ Choose your preferred design
рҹ“Ӣ PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	WomenвҖҷs Stockings
Material	Nylon / Polyester
Size	One Size (Stretch Fit)
Length	Approx. 80вҖ“110 cm
Pattern	Floral Lace
Thickness	Standard
Gender	Women
Quantity	1 Pair
Style	Fashion Hosiery
рҹ“Ұ PACKAGE INCLUDES
вң”  1 x PantyhoseпјҲDoes not contain thong underwearпјү
рҹ”Ҙ MULTI-BUY OFFERS
рҹ’° Buy More Save More
рҹ’° Quantity discounts available
Check offers above for the latest deals
рҹҡҡ UK SHIPPING
вң… FREE UK Delivery
вң… Fast Dispatch
вң… Discreet Packaging
вң… Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EWAAAeSwk2dp08uK/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FlcAAeSwjX1p08uJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/l2UAAeSwnLRp08uJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y6IAAeSwU4Jp08uJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1H4AAeSwCoRp08uJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sHcAAeSw-2Bp08uJ/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092451</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092123</sku><product_name>Hold Ups stockings elasticated lace top thigh high Sheer Many colours very sexy</product_name><description>рҹ”Ҙ PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Add elegance and style to your outfit with these WomenвҖҷs Sheer Lace Stay-Up Thigh High Stockings. Designed with soft stretch fabric and a beautiful lace trim, these stockings provide a secure yet comfortable fit while enhancing your fashion look.

Perfect for evening wear, parties, special occasions, or everyday styling, these fashionable hold-up stockings are a must-have addition to any wardrobe.

вӯҗ KEY FEATURES
вң… Elegant Lace Top вҖ“ Stylish floral lace trim design
вң… Stay-Up Hold Design вҖ“ Elastic band helps stockings stay securely in place
вң… Soft Sheer Fabric вҖ“ Lightweight and breathable material
вң… Stretch Fit Material вҖ“ Flexible design for comfortable wear
вң… Thigh High Length вҖ“ Modern fashionable style
вң… Multiple Colours Available вҖ“ Choose your preferred style
вң… Perfect For Many Occasions вҖ“ Ideal for parties, evenings, and fashion outfits
рҹ“Ӣ PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	WomenвҖҷs Stockings
Style	Stay-Up / Hold-Ups
Material	Nylon / Spandex
Size	One Size (Stretch Fit вҖ“ fits most)
Length	Thigh High
Pattern	Solid with Lace Top
Thickness	Thin / Sheer
Colours	Black, White, Red, Purple, Pink, Brown
Department	Women
Condition	New 
рҹ“Ұ PACKAGE INCLUDES
вң” 1 Г— Pair WomenвҖҷs Lace Stockings
рҹ”Ҙ MULTI-BUY OFFERS
рҹ’° Buy More Save More
рҹ’° Quantity discounts available
Check the offer section above for latest deals
рҹҡҡ UK SHIPPING
вң… FREE UK Delivery
вң… Fast Dispatch
вң… Discreet Packaging
вң… Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5v8AAeSwiJ5p16Vm/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6HEAAeSwwtlp16Vn/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/IFUAAeSwZ81p16Vn/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EcsAAeSwhHJp16Vn/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1fwAAeSwamJp16Vq/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TOYAAeSwJVdp16Vn/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092123</ean><condition>New</condition><price>7.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092482</sku><product_name>Men's Leather Cross Body Messenger Shoulder Bag Handbag Travel Work Business Bag</product_name><description>рҹ”Ҙ PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Upgrade your everyday style with this Rugged Vintage Texture Shoulder Bag, designed for daily use, work, travel, and casual outings. Made from high-quality PU leather, this bag offers durability with a classic vintage finish.

Featuring a lightweight build and adjustable shoulder strap, it can be worn comfortably as a shoulder bag or crossbody bag. Perfect for keeping your essentials organised while maintaining a stylish look.

вӯҗ KEY FEATURES
вң… Vintage Leather Look вҖ“ Stylish rugged design for everyday wear
вң… Lightweight &amp; Comfortable вҖ“ Ideal for long-term use
вң… Adjustable Strap вҖ“ Wear as shoulder or crossbody bag
вң… Durable PU Leather вҖ“ Strong and long-lasting material
вң… Spacious Storage вҖ“ Fits phone, wallet, keys, and essentials
вң… Internal Pockets вҖ“ Keeps items organised
вң… Multi-Purpose Use вҖ“ Perfect for work, travel, school, and daily use
вң… Unisex Design вҖ“ Suitable for men and women
рҹ“Ӣ PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Shoulder / Crossbody Bag
Style	Casual / Business / Vintage
Material	PU Leather
Lining Material	Polyester
Closure Type	Zip (varies by model)
Strap Type	Adjustable
Colours Available	Black, Brown, Khaki
Gender	Unisex
Occasion	Work / Travel / Daily Use
рҹ“Ұ PACKAGE INCLUDES
вң” 1 Г— Shoulder Crossbody Bag
рҹ”Ҙ MULTI-BUY OFFERS
рҹ’° Buy More Save More
рҹ’° Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals
рҹҡҡ UK SHIPPING
вң… FREE UK Delivery
вң… Fast Dispatch
вң… Secure Packaging
вң… Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/V4sAAeSwOqpp2RX4/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jZMAAeSw4u1p2RX4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ALQAAeSwKRRp2RX5/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VaAAAeSwpFxp2RX4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5x0AAeSwFd5p2RX4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/GEMAAeSwf5Np2RX5/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092482</ean><condition>New</condition><price>19.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092499</sku><product_name>Strong Vacuum Suction Cup Hook Shower Towel-Holder Hooks for Bathroom Kitchen UK</product_name><description>рҹ”Ҙ PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Organise your space easily with these Vacuum Suction Cup Hooks, designed to provide a strong hold without drilling or damaging your walls. Made from premium 304 stainless steel, these hooks are perfect for bathrooms, kitchens, and home organisation.

With powerful suction grip and a modern design, they securely hold towels, bags, and accessories on smooth surfaces while keeping your space neat and clutter-free.

вӯҗ KEY FEATURES
вң… No Drilling Required вҖ“ Easy installation without tools or wall damage
вң… Strong Suction Power вҖ“ Holds up to approx. 15 lbs (6.8 kg)
вң… Waterproof &amp; Rustproof вҖ“ Ideal for bathroom and kitchen use
вң… Durable Stainless Steel вҖ“ Corrosion-resistant and long-lasting
вң… Modern Design вҖ“ Matches any home dГ©cor style
вң… Reusable &amp; Removable вҖ“ Easy to reposition without marks
вң… Anti-Slip Hook вҖ“ Secure grip for hanging items safely
рҹ“Ӣ PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Suction Cup Hook
Material	304 Stainless Steel
Installation	Vacuum Suction (No Drill)
Load Capacity	Up to 15 lbs (approx.)
Colour Options	Silver, Black, Gold, White
Use	Bathroom, Kitchen, Home Organisation
рҹҺҜ IDEAL FOR
вң” Towels &amp; bath accessories
вң” Kitchen utensils
вң” Handbags &amp; keys
вң” Clothes &amp; hats
вң” Shower accessories
рҹ“Ұ PACKAGE OPTIONS
вң” 1 Г— Hook
вң” 2 Г— Hooks (Value Pack)
вҡ пёҸ INSTALLATION TIPS
Suitable for smooth surfaces only (tiles, glass, metal, wood)
Not suitable for painted or rough walls
Press firmly and wait 24 hours before use
рҹ”Ҙ MULTI-BUY OFFERS
рҹ’° Buy More Save More
рҹ’° Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AH0AAeSwhHJp3luF/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LO0AAeSwQOlp3luH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sWwAAeSwYOtp3luH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VpwAAeSw7T5p3luG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/KxoAAeSwKuRp3luG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/foQAAeSwibJp3luG/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092499</ean><condition>New</condition><price>22.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092505</sku><product_name>Mens Body Shaper Compression Vest Slimming Shirt Tank Chest Belly Men's Waist UK</product_name><description>рҹ”Ҙ PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Achieve a more confident look instantly with this MenвҖҷs Slimming Compression Vest, designed to shape your chest, flatten your stomach, and support better posture. Made from a breathable stretch fabric, this vest provides firm compression while remaining comfortable for all-day wear.

Perfect for daily wear, gym workouts, or under clothing for a slimmer appearance. Lightweight, flexible, and discreet under shirts for everyday confidence.

вӯҗ KEY FEATURES
вң… Instant Slimming Effect вҖ“ Flattens belly and shapes chest
вң… Compression Fit Design вҖ“ Supports posture and core
вң… Breathable Fabric вҖ“ Comfortable for all-day wear
вң… Seamless Under Clothing вҖ“ Invisible under shirts
вң… High Elastic Material вҖ“ Flexible body-contouring fit
вң… Lightweight &amp; Comfortable вҖ“ Ideal for daily or sports use
вң… Multi-Purpose Wear вҖ“ Gym, running, work, or casual wear
рҹ“Ӣ PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	MenвҖҷs Compression Vest / Body Shaper
Material	Polyester
Fabric Type	Breathable Stretch
Style	Sleeveless Vest
Fit	Slim Compression Fit
Colours	Black, White
Sizes	M, L, XL, XXL
Pattern	Solid
Care	Machine Washable
Condition	New 
рҹ“Ң SIZE TIP
Choose one size up for a more comfortable fit.

рҹҺҜ IDEAL FOR
вң” Daily wear under shirts
вң” Gym &amp; fitness training
вң” Running, cycling, workouts
вң” Body shaping &amp; posture support
вң” Confidence boosting appearance
рҹ“Ұ PACKAGE INCLUDES
вң” 1 Г— MenвҖҷs Compression Vest
рҹ”Ҙ MULTI-BUY OFFERS
рҹ’° Buy More Save More
рҹ’° Quantity discounts available
Check offers above for the latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rCoAAeSwmlFp4QUN/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1hUAAeSwT05p4QUL/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jHwAAeSweM9p4QUN/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FWcAAeSwvsRp4QUN/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iPwAAeSwLqJp4QUM/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TP0AAeSwqZVp4QUM/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092505</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092512</sku><product_name>5 Pack Womens Sexy Knickers Underwear Ladies Lace Panties Seamless Briefs Pants</product_name><description>рҹ”Ҙ PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Refresh your essentials with this 5 Pack WomenвҖҷs Cotton Lace Briefs Set, designed for everyday comfort with a stylish feminine touch. Made from a soft cotton-rich stretch fabric, these knickers offer breathable comfort, flexible fit, and delicate lace trim.

Perfect for daily wear, work, travel, or casual comfort, these briefs combine practicality with elegant style while providing a smooth and comfortable fit under clothing.

вӯҗ KEY FEATURES
вң… 5 Pack Value Set вҖ“ Includes 5 assorted colours/styles
вң… Soft Cotton Rich Fabric вҖ“ Comfortable and breathable feel
вң… 100% Cotton Crotch Lining вҖ“ Extra freshness and hygiene
вң… Low Waist Design вҖ“ Modern flattering fit
вң… Stretch Material вҖ“ Flexible comfort for all-day wear
вң… Lace Trim Finish вҖ“ Elegant, feminine detail
вң… Lightweight &amp; Breathable вҖ“ Ideal for everyday use
вң… Comfort Fit Brief Style вҖ“ Smooth under clothing
рҹҺЁ COLOUR OPTIONS
рҹҢҲ Mixed Colour Packs Available

рҹ“Ң Due to monitor and lighting differences, actual colours may vary slightly from images.

рҹ“Ӣ PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	WomenвҖҷs Knickers / Briefs
Style	Low Waist Briefs
Material	95% Cotton / 5% Spandex
Crotch Fabric	100% Cotton
Decoration	Lace Trim
Pattern	Solid Colours
Fit	Regular Stretch Fit
Sizes Available	M, L, XL
Quantity	5 Pieces Set
рҹ“Ҹ SIZE GUIDE
рҹ“Ң Asian sizing may run smaller than UK/EU sizes. Please consider choosing one size up for best comfort.

M вҖ“ Suitable for Small
L вҖ“ Suitable for Medium
XL вҖ“ Suitable for Large
рҹ“Ұ PACKAGE INCLUDES
вң” 5 Г— WomenвҖҷs Cotton Lace Briefs (Mixed / Selected Colours)
рҹҺҜ PERFECT FOR
вң” Everyday wear
вң” Work &amp; office use
вң” Travel
вң” Comfortable daily essentials
вң” Gift idea
рҹ”Ҙ MULTI-BUY OFFERS
рҹ’° Buy More Save More
рҹ’° Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/C4EAAeSwE2Fp421f/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/L6QAAeSwyXBp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/G2AAAeSwPw9p421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WsMAAeSwXCBp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FoIAAeSwrHRp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/snkAAeSwX9xp421h/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092512</ean><condition>New</condition><price>16.99</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091829</sku><product_name>Portable Zipper Eye Glasses Hard Case Sunglass Reading Cover Box Protector Gift</product_name><description>рҹ”Ҙ PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Keep your glasses safe and stylish with this Fashion Denim Fabric Glasses Case. Made from high-quality cotton denim, this soft-shell case features a smooth zipper closure and a trendy patchwork pattern. Perfect for sunglasses, reading glasses, or prescription eyewear.

The lightweight yet protective design prevents scratches, dust, and damage while you're on the go. A must-have accessory for anyone who wants to keep their glasses organized and protected.

вӯҗ KEY FEATURES
рҹ”№ Premium Denim Fabric вҖ“ High-quality cotton, soft yet durable
рҹ”№ Zipper Closure вҖ“ Secure, smooth-gliding zipper keeps glasses safely inside
рҹ”№ Scratch Protection вҖ“ Soft interior lining prevents lens scratches
рҹ”№ Fashion Patchwork Design вҖ“ Trendy and unisex style for men and women
рҹ”№ Universal Size вҖ“ Fits most sunglasses, reading glasses, and prescription eyewear
рҹ”№ Lightweight &amp; Portable вҖ“ Easy to carry in purse, backpack, or pocket
рҹ”№ Great Gift Idea вҖ“ Perfect for glasses wearers, travelers, or fashion lovers
рҹ“Ӣ PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Soft Shell Eyeglasses Case / Sunglasses Pouch
Material	Denim Fabric (Cotton) вҖ“ No high-concerned chemicals
Closure	Zipper
Pattern Type	Patchwork
Dimensions (approx.)	Length: 16cm (6.3вҖі), Width: 6cm (2.4вҖі), Height: 3.5cm (1.4вҖі)
Weight	Approx. 106g (3.7 oz)
Gender	Unisex
Brand	UNBRANDED
Origin	China
Package Included	1 Г— Eyeglasses Box / Case</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y90AAeSwKuRp55JU/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/D28AAeSwkJNp55JU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yS4AAeSwAnFp55JU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BREAAeSwrclp55JU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5-4AAeSw7LFp55JU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Bz8AAeSwkXBp55JU/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834091829</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product></products>